<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethics on Bulletin</title>
    <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/tags/ethics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethics on Bulletin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 21:36:17 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://machoo-l.github.io/tags/ethics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Person as the Subject and Object of Action</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/10-cbc-love-and-responsibility-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 21:36:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/10-cbc-love-and-responsibility-1/</guid>
      <description>The world is composed of subjects and objects. A subject is an entity that exists and acts in a certain way. An object is an entity to be acted upon. Every subject also exists as on object.
Man is &amp;lsquo;somebody&amp;rsquo; which sets him apart from every other entity which is an object that is &amp;lsquo;something.&amp;rsquo; We would hesitate to call an animal a thing but recognize them as subjects of a particular species.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/9-vulnerability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:55:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/9-vulnerability/</guid>
      <description>We guard our hearts because we are weak and the world is cruel. You are afraid of being naked and hide your insecurities from others because you fear the pain of judgement. It takes tremendous trust to be vulnerable with someone. You lay bare your heart and all your weakness, trusting that they do not hurt you in your vulnerablility.
It is important to show others love when they are at their lowest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Reliance</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/6-self-reliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:42:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/6-self-reliance/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Food and Self-Reliance</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/4-fast-food-and-self-reliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 22:14:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/4-fast-food-and-self-reliance/</guid>
      <description>Fast food makes you reliant. The convenience of fast food distracts your attention from time spent developing important skills like cooking. Years of consuming fast food makes you reliant on external entities for living.
The Dunkin&amp;rsquo; down your block could close down suddenly one day and you start to panic because you don&amp;rsquo;t know how you&amp;rsquo;ll get through the day without coffee in the morning. If only you invested some time into your future by buying a coffee machine and learning to make your own coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Responsibility</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/3-love-and-responsibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 22:56:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/3-love-and-responsibility/</guid>
      <description>We have a duty to love one another. Surrendering oneself to another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
