<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>  on Bulletin</title>
    <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in   on Bulletin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 12:55:21 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://machoo-l.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Denim Sewing Ideas</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/15-sewing-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 12:55:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/15-sewing-ideas/</guid>
      <description> Polo Ralph Lauren Denim Vest Polo Ralph Lauren Denim Vest Fit Louis Vuitton Speedy Bandouliere 25 Shape </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truth of Masculinity; Being Too Afraid To Do Anything Because the Internet and College Makes You Dumb as Hell</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/14-truth-of-masculinity-and-being-afraid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 23:49:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/14-truth-of-masculinity-and-being-afraid/</guid>
      <description>Effeminacy is preferring your pleasure over doing what is difficult. It is effeminate for men to take pleasure in lacking responsibility. Women have no respect for effeminate men who are easily controlled. Too often when men get into a relationship they will give in to the woman&amp;rsquo;s complaining to have some peace and quiet. This weakness shows her that she can push the man around and have her way.
Men must mature by suffering and struggling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Together Man and Woman</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/13-the-role-of-men-and-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/13-the-role-of-men-and-women/</guid>
      <description>Men and women are meant for each other. Men are fulfilled in giving their all to women and women are fulfilled in gifting themselves to men. The differences between men and women make us perfect complements.
Every human person is set apart from all the creatures and objects of the world. Dolphins and monkeys are intelligent animals, but they lack the interior life that comes from personhood. The interior allows a person to choose a goal that he deems to be good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Person as the Subject and Object of Action</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/11-cbc-love-and-responsibility-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 21:36:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/11-cbc-love-and-responsibility-1/</guid>
      <description>The world is composed of subjects and objects. A subject is an entity that exists and acts in a certain way. An object is an entity to be acted upon. Every subject also exists as on object.
Man is &amp;lsquo;somebody&amp;rsquo; which sets him apart from every other entity which is an object that is &amp;lsquo;something.&amp;rsquo; We would hesitate to call an animal a thing but recognize them as subjects of a particular species.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media, Pop Culture Brain and Self-Reflection</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/10-social-media-and-self-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 04:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/10-social-media-and-self-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Modern culture evolves rapidly, adding and removing new terms and conditions you must comply with. There is always a new fad to see and share with your friends. It&amp;rsquo;s dizzying to keep up with it all. Every day is the same endless cycle of scrolling through slightly interesting posts that are, in the end, empty and unfulfilling.
Social media is designed to be an deep void of nothing. Infinite scrolling apps feed you a constant stream of stimulation that leaves you craving for more when you get off your phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/9-vulnerability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 08:55:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/9-vulnerability/</guid>
      <description>We guard our hearts because we are weak and the world is cruel. You are afraid of being naked and hide your insecurities from others because you fear the pain of judgement. It takes tremendous trust to be vulnerable with someone. You lay bare your heart and all your weakness, trusting that they do not hurt you in your vulnerablility.
It is important to show others love when they are at their lowest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Server</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/8-minecraft-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:01:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/8-minecraft-server/</guid>
      <description>Minecraft servers are single threaded so having more CPU cores will not improve the server&amp;rsquo;s performance. Articles recommend 1GB to 2GB of allocated RAM for 10 people on a server.
Client Side (1.20.1) Fabric is mod loader for Minecraft.
(1.20.1) OptiFine is an optimization mod for better performance. Usually you install OptiFine on its own without the Fabric mod loader but since we want voice chat we will need to supplement it with OptiFabric.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prospect First Car</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/7-prospect-first-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:48:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/7-prospect-first-car/</guid>
      <description>Reliable and good looking cars.
Honda Accord Lexus LS 400 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Food and Self-Reliance</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/4-fast-food-and-self-reliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 22:14:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/4-fast-food-and-self-reliance/</guid>
      <description>Fast food makes you reliant. The convenience of fast food distracts your attention from time spent developing important skills like cooking. Years of consuming fast food makes you reliant on external entities for living.
The Dunkin&amp;rsquo; down your block could close down suddenly one day and you start to panic because you don&amp;rsquo;t know how you&amp;rsquo;ll get through the day without coffee in the morning. If only you invested some time into your future by buying a coffee machine and learning to make your own coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Responsibility</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/3-love-and-responsibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 22:56:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/3-love-and-responsibility/</guid>
      <description>We have a duty to love one another. Surrendering oneself to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer of Surrender</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/2-prayer-of-surrender/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 22:55:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/2-prayer-of-surrender/</guid>
      <description>Lord Jesus Christ, take all my freedom, my understanding, and my will. All that I have and cherish you have given to me. I surrender it all to be guided by your will. Your love and your grace are wealth enough for me. Give me these, Lord Jesus, and I ask for nothing more. Amen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Server</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/1-home-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 22:47:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/1-home-server/</guid>
      <description>I want to host a permanent Minecraft server for me and my friends to play. Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s tiny business computers seem like a good choice to host the server. It can also be used for a Plex server to stream shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/0-my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 16:40:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/posts/0-my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Apetite curbing is a difficult today. I probably ate over 3000 calories today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m Matthew Le. I appreciate you for visiting my webpage and I hope you learn something new.
I created this website to learn web development and to improve my eloquence in writing. As our lives grow ever consumed by the internet we neglect the cultivation of essential personal skills. I desire to spread goodness in the world through connection and self-giving.
I have plans to add commenting and display other projects that I work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Text!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://machoo-l.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://machoo-l.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Text!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
